Because I've had such a different experience in this country than you.
Because as a black woman, the government is so much of my life.
And it always has been.
Like, the government literally said that black men couldn't even be in the house
or else women could not get welfare.
And that's a big reason why there's such a chasm between black women and black men in this generation.
So I think that there's just a lot to understand for, like,
why people are talking the way they're talking about different things.
I understand why you're talking the way you're talking.
Because I know...
I just don't understand what am I talking about.
I just said, I believe in this country.
Yes.
And you don't.
You can say that in a way that I cannot.
Because you've had a different experience.
Because this country is here for you.
This country ain't here for me in the same way, sis.
It isn't.
And you, as a trans person, have to also identify the fact that this country hasn't been here for trans
until, like, maybe 2 o'clock today.
So that's a constant.
That's a constant.
At this dinner were me, Caitlyn Jenner, Margaret Cho, Katy Perry,
Van Jones, Ina Navarro, Sally Cohn.
The point of contention that you all are seeing here is after I had made the statement
that Donald Trump wants to be the next Hitler.
And everybody at the table was like,
someone went so far as to say, it's not like he's sending people to gas chambers.
I said, well, Hitler didn't start with gas chambers.
Here we are in 2025.
And we are watching Donald Trump recreate in legislation and in his own image,
a mimicry of the fascism of the Third Reich.
Now, Caitlyn Jenner was pouting throughout this whole thing.
And Van Jones was like, please, Caitlyn, please say something.
Say something.
I don't know why her point of view was so relevant.
Nonetheless, she chimed in and said, I'm just very offended that someone would say such a terrible
thing about my president.
I'm a U.S. citizen.
I love this country.
This government has never been harmful to my life.
Anywho, I have committed myself to always being the person in these spaces who refuses
to allow politeness to impede progress.
So what you're seeing here on Surrounded ain't nothing new.
And I hope that we can all make it our business to not just be shiny, happy people in the midst
of very dark times.
We can't just see the light.
We got to be the light.